I went there.
We made it for the New Year!
Yay!
Thank you!
Thank you! Thank you for coming.
It's great to see you all here.
It's like we're one step ahead of you.
It's like the members are going to see it.
I'd like to watch it with you.
I've seen it.
It's the first time the members have seen it.
I'd like to see it.
I'm going to watch this with Obikomen.
It's so cute!
Is it going to be an ogihana pose?
Ogihana pose
Certainly, it's a goo bun.
Okay, the first one has a Coco Coco card.
Yes!
Here it is.
Announcement!
There are 5 kinds of cards.
There are 5 kinds?
Random.
I guess so.
It's so dense!
What?
Dark.
It's pretty.
What are we gonna do?
What do we do?
Oh, my God!
He's so good with the camera.
He only eats this once or twice.
That's great.
It's like a picture. It's kind of picturesque.
Aah!
Aaah!
Caw!
Aaaaah!
Aah!
Oh, no!
Oh, my God!
Aah!
What is it?
What is this?
Oh!
That was long.
Here idades.
Oh Ellie
More falar
глаз должны
Camera!
O разные
Oph...
personajes
Ye... Yay!
Aah!
Yaş and
spirit
Wow!
That's great!
And my guess, this one.
You!
I love it!
I'm hiding.
Really?
Oh, my gosh!
This is my favorite.
It's like...
Thank you!
Thank you so much.
They're all so cute.
What?
I'll take it with your autograph.
Thank you!
I'm so happy!
That's great.
It's true.
I only see one.
It's the page I'm looking at.
He's so cute.
I'll see you soon.
I'm so happy!
Ogi Hana's first photo book, Ogi Hana, was released on May 8th.
Thank you very much!
What a surprise! We're currently accepting applications for an additional book signing and online signing.
Please apply for it!
Please be our guest!
Be our guest!
Please do! f